

MD. JANNATUL NAEEM

COMPUTER ENGINEER

219/Da, R#4, B#D, Banasree Rampura, Dhaka-1219

Contact: 01708355634 jannatulnaeem042@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/jannatulnaeem

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To utilize my technical skills and provide a professional service to the organization by applying and honing my knowledge and working in a challenging and motivating working environment.

CAREER SUMMARY

Computer engineering graduate with an emphasis in software, network security, and database management over Windows and Linux. Experienced in results-driven IT consultancy with 4 years of experience in strategic problem-solving. Dedicated to implementing new strategies and improving communications between departments.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

SS Media Vision

Media Production House, Event Management & IT Solution January 2018 - Present

IT Consultant

- Implementing technological solutions to meet business needs.
- Diagnosing IT system problems, inefficiencies & weaknesses.
- Monitoring the success of IT solutions.

VOLUNTEERING EXPERIENCE

UITS Computer Club

UITS Authorized Computer & IT Based Campus Club June 2021- Present

Farhanas' Brainstation

LinkedIn based career, professionalism and skill developing platform

January 2022- Present

EDUCATION

University f Information Technology & Sciences (UITS) 2018 - 2022

Khulna Public College 2015 - 2017

Shiromoni Alim Madrasah Khulna 2013-2015

Senior Executive (Microsoft Wing)

- To manage Microsoft's programs on the university campus & virtual platforms.
- To build awareness among students about Microsoft's innovative programs through UITS Computer Club.
- To organize intra varsity cultural events.

Social Media Manager

- To manage social media platforms like LinkedIn and Facebook.
- To design & develop social media posts, polls, documents & communicate with people to spread awareness about career.
- To Copywrite and analyze digital marketing strategies and work for further development of the specific platforms.

BSc in Computer Science and Engineering (CSE)

- · Inventory Management Software Development
- ChatsApp Android App Development
- Campus Events Management Software Development

Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC)

- · School of Science
- GPA 4.33 out of 5.00

Dakhil (SSC)

- · School of Science
- GPA 5.00 out of 5.00

CORE SKILLS

- Teamwork & Web Design & Applications planning, Software Database Logical Thinking Development designing & deployment Development Management

TECHNICAL SKILLS

• C, C++ • JAVA • HTML • CSS • BOOTSRAP 5 • MYSQL • JQUERY • JS • WORDPRESS

SOFTWARE SKILLS

MS WORD
 MS EXCEL
 POWERPOINT
 CANVA
 MS ACCESS
 PHOTOSHOP

TRAINING

Learning & Earning
Development Project (LEDP)
2021 (4 Month)

Mohammad Ali Computer Institute 2015 (6 Month)

Bohubrihi Online Course 2021

Web Design & Development

- HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, JavaScript, JQuery
- WordPress CMS

MS Office Application & Database Management

- MS Word, Access, Excel, PowerPoint, MySQL
- GPA 5.00 out of 5.00

Digital Marketing

- Social Media Marketing
- Google Adsense, E-mail Marketing etc.

KEY PROFICIENCIES

Verbal and Written Communication in Bangla & English fluently, Team Work, Demand Management, Problem-Solving Skills in a Super Changing Environment, Management, Hardware & Software Support, Quick Learner, Leadership, Negotiation, Algorithms & Data Structures, Creative Thinking, and Collaboration.

AWARDS & APPRECIATIONS

- Best Volunteer, ZERO-ONE FEST 3, 2019
- Best Technical Support, ZERO-ONE FEST 4, 2020
- Appreciated for organizing ZERO ONE FEST 4, 2020 Organized by UITS Computer Club
- Appreciated for organizing Microsoft "Cloud: Start" Session, 2021 Organized by UITS Computer Club
- GOVT. Junior Dakhil Certificate Scholarship, 2013

REFERANCES

Mr. AL Imtiaz

Assistant Professor & Head, Department of CSE, University of Information Technology & Sciences (UITS)

Contact: 01715135517 Email: al.imtiaz@yahoo.com

SM Shariful Islam

Managing Director Banasree Builders Limited

Contact: 01712754575

Email: ssmediavisionbd@gmail.com